Guide to the Consumer Reports Archives records RL.11772
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Staff and Affiliate Biographies, 1924-2015 and undated; 3
  - Peterson, Esther (speeches), 1964; 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Pittle, David, 1988-2000 (Box 9)
  - Pollak, George A., 1975 (Box 9)
  - Reeves, Albert, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Reich, Edward, 1937-1979 (Box 9)
  - Reis, Bernard, 1932-1978; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Rice, Florence, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Richards, Henry E., 1948-1978 (Box 9)
  - Ross, Madeline (Mrs. Jack Medoff), 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Sandbach, Walker, 1971-1975 (Box 9)
  - Schlink, Frederick J., 1926-1995 (Box 9)
  - Schuck, Peter H., 1972-1975 (Box 9)
  - Schulkind, Adelaide, 1972-1974 (Box 9)
  - Schoenfeld, David, 1966-1982 (Box 9)
  - Shainwald, Sidney, 1972-2009 (Box 9)
  - Shainwald, Sybil, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Shapiro, Esther, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Shearer, Gail, 1975-2008 (Box 9)
  - Shedlovsky, Theodore, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Silber, Norman, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Silbergeld, Mark, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Smith, Robert L., 1934-1971 (Box 9)
  - Snyder, Harry, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Southworth, Herman, 1935-1937 and undated (Box 9)
  - Steele, Dorothy, 1963-1979 (Box 9)
  - Strong, Lydia Altschuler, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Swankin, David, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Tallman, David, undated (Box 9)
  - Tedori, Fred, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Thorelli, Hans B., 1965-1977 (Box 9)
  - Ulman, Joseph N., undated (Box 9)
  - Ware, Caroline, 1946-1998 (Box 9)
  - Warne, Colston, 1945-1980; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Webber, Harold D., 1978 (Box 9)
  - Weir, Marion, 1970-1978 (Box 9)
  - Whitehill, Jean, undated (Box 9)
  - Who's That? Photo directory, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Woodhouse, Chase Going, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Wolfe, Allis--Interviews for book on Persia Campbell, 1980 (Box 9)
    Includes: Arthur Startz, Aurelia Toyer Miller, Burton Agata, Harold Wattel, W. Averell Harriman
- Reference Card Files, 1936-1992 and undated; 4
  Includes biographical cards, bibliographies, subject and organizational files, and a subject index to magazine articles up through the early 1990s. Also includes microfiche files on various magazines, technical journals, research reports and library database extraction.
  - General Files, 1936-1992 and undated; 9
    - Bibliography of consumer movement, undated (Box 11)
    - Biographical and organizational files, undated (Box 12)
    - Biographical index and cross-reference; Subject file, undated (Box 13)
    - Books by author (reference library), undated (Box 14)
    - Microfiche--Journals, 1960-1992 (Box 15)
      Includes: American Dietetic Association Journal 1975-1978; American Journal of Clinical Nutrition 1970-1975; Consumer Bulletin 1960-1973; Consumer Reports 1978-1992
    - Microfiche--Journals, 1936-1990 (Box 16)
      Includes: Consumer Reports 1936-1980; various test reports 1981; Which? 1970-1975; Consumers Research Magazine 1974-1981; Westcat (Westchester Library System) alphabetical file 1987-1990
    - Microfiche--Journals, 1972-1987 (Box 17)
      Includes: Westcat (Westchester Library System) alphabetical file 1987; Money Magazine 1972-1981
    - Microfiche--Journals, 1972-1987 (Box 18)
      Includes: Ms. 1972-1981; Rtecs Quarterly 1987; set of technical reports from New York Public Library 1970s-1985
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19)
      Includes: CR publications; bibliographies; films; filmstrips; microfilm; oral history interviews; recordings; videotapes; personnel addresses
  - Magazine Index, 1936-1980; 10
    - A-C, 1936-1950 (Box 20)
    - D-H, 1936-1950 (Box 21)
    - I-O, 1936-1950 (Box 22)
    - P-S, 1936-1950 (Box 23)
    - T-Z, 1936-1950 (Box 24)
    - A, 1951-1965 (Box 25)
    - B-Cr, 1951-1965 (Box 26)
    - Cr-F, 1951-1965 (Box 27)
    - G-Li, 1951-1965 (Box 28)
    - Lo-Pri, 1951-1965 (Box 29)
    - Pri-S, 1951-1965 (Box 30)
    - T-Z, 1951-1965 (Box 31)
    - A-F, 1966-1972 (Box 32)
    - G-Z, 1966-1972 (Box 33)
    - A-D, 1973-1980 (Box 34)
    - E-O, 1973-1980 (Box 35)
    - P-Z, 1973-1980 (Box 36)